kia-buzz.com 2009-12-01

# Privacy Policy

Kia Motors Corporation’s (“KMC”) privacy policy (the “Policy”) governs the information you provide during your visits to Kia-BUZZ (the “Blog”)  **If you do not agree with the policy, please do not use this Blog.**  

**Copyright**

All information provided on the Blog is protected by copyright.  You may only use the information provided on the Blog for personal purposes.  KMC does not authorize the reproduction, adaptation or publishing of any of the materials provided by the Blog in whole or in part for any reasons without KMC’s written authorization.  The Kia mark and design and its vehicle names and their logo designs are registered trademarks of Kia Motors Corporation.  These marks and logos may not be used, downloaded, copied or distributed in any way. 

**No Guarantee**

KMC does not guarantee the confidentiality of the use of the Blog.  KMC shall not assume responsibility for any damage or injury suffered as a result of any breach of confidentiality resulting from your use of the Blog. 

**Collection of Personal Information**

There are times when where KMC requests your personal information in order to provide you with better service such as access to the Blog, the receipt of Blog entry alerts, promotions and newsletters.  Depending on the type of service, KMC might request your name, mailing address, email address, phone number, date of birth and others.  You can decline to submit personal information to any of our services, in which case KMC may not be able to provide those services to you.   

Please be noted that your personal information may be shared with our business partners to aid in providing with the best service.  KMC may also share your information with companies associated with KMC’s regional headquarters, affiliated companies, subsidiaries, private distributors, and authorized dealers.  We require of these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with the Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 

Please be noted that KMC reserves the right to disclose any personally identifiable information we collect through the Blog if we are required to do so by law or if we have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, deception, security, or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of KMC, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.

**Blog Usage**

It is possible for you to visit the Blog and receive information regarding KMC and related news without providing us with any of your personal information.  When you use the Blog, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website.  These server logs may include information such as your web request or visit, your prior web site address, your next web site address, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your visit or posting and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.   
The collected and stored information may be used to calculate statistic measures of the Blog activity so we are able to recognize our visitors and develop ways to improve the blog and your visits.

**Underage Privacy**

Kia-BUZZ will not knowingly collect personal information from anyone under 13 years of age.

**Information Security**

KMC takes appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data.  These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. 

We restrict access to personal information to KMC employees, contractors, subsidiary employees, and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve or respond to the blog.  These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

**Use of Cookies**

Kia-BUZZ may collect and store information about you on your computer through the form of an internet “cookie.”  A “cookie” is a small file of characters that is stored in your computer after your first visit, which uniquely identifies your browser.  For example, in order to leave a comment, you are required to enter your name, email address and as a result, it will be filled automatically through the use of a “cookie.”  “Cookies” are used to provide you with a more personal experience on Kia-BUZZ.  Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent.  Some Blog features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled or deleted.

**Links**

Kia-BUZZ contains links to third party sites not controlled by KMC or covered by this privacy statement, such as other blogs.  KMC does not warrant any information, offers, or advertisements provided by such blogs provided via hyperlinks on Kia-BUZZ.  Please check the privacy policy of the other blogs before you decide to visit them and provide any personal information on the site. 

**Contact Us**

Protecting your privacy online is an evolving area, and KMC’s Web sites and their affiliate’s websites are constantly evolving to meet these demands.

If you have any comments or questions regarding our Policy, or KMC’s treatment of personal information, please contact [Kia-BUZZ editor](mailto:dongpabj@kia.co.kr). **While we cannot guarantee privacy perfection, we will address any issue to the best of our abilities.** When we receive written complaints, it is our policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns.  We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between KMC and an individual.

**Changes to This Policy**

Please note that the Policy may change from time to time.  We will post any Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice.  Each version of this policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date, and we will also keep our prior versions of this Policy in an archive for your review. 

Kia Forte (Cerato) Koup
